contentpop.com 2007-10-11

# Privacy Policy For Content Pop

| 

## Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: August 27, 2006**

ContentPop.com is soley owned by the BLUE GUMBO LLC company.

The following Privacy Policy governs ContentPop.com's online information collection practices. Specifically, it outlines the types of information that ContentPop.com gathers about you while you are using the ContentPop.com website (the "Service"), and the ways in which ContentPop.com uses and doesn’t use this information. This Privacy Policy, including the children’s privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail). In addition, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any activities (online or otherwise) of the BLUE GUMBO company.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting the ContentPop.com website, you agree that your use of our Service, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we'll post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the ContentPop.com website after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: 

Blue Gumbo  
523 East Beth Drive  
Phoenix, AZ 85042 

What Information is Collected About Visitors? 

The information that ContentPop.com collects about you while you are using the Service falls into two general categories: 

  1. Information You Provide to Us - ContentPop.com may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply either while on the ContentPop.com website or in responding via email in connection with a feature provided on the ContentPop.com website. Some examples of this type of information include demographic information that you electronically submit when you sign up for access to certain features on the Service, information (such as your name or email address) that you electronically submit that you post on message boards on the ContentPop.com website, and information contained in search requests or questions that you submit to the ContentPop.com website. If you decline to supply or provide ContentPop.com with certain information while using the Service, you may not be able to use or participate in some or all of the features offered through the Service.
  2. Information that is Automatically Collected - ContentPop.com also collects and stores information that is generated automatically as you navigate through the ContentPop.com website. For example, to enhance your experience on the ContentPop.com website, ContentPop.com uses a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie." Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the ContentPop.com site, cookies help us track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the ContentPop.com site where you have entered preference information before. ContentPop.com also uses web beacons (also known as "single-pixel GIFs") to access cookies and to count users who visit the ContentPop.com site or open ContentPop.com's HTML-formatted email messages. Another example of information that ContentPop.com automatically collects as you navigate the ContentPop.com site is information about your computer's connection to the Internet. This information allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on the ContentPop.com site.

## How is this Information Used? 

ContentPop.com uses the information it collects from you while you are using the Service in a variety of ways, including using the information to customize features and advertising that appear on the ContentPop.com website. We also may provide your information to third parties, such as service providers, contractors, and advertisers, for a variety of purposes. For example, we may provide our advertisers with information about you and other visitors that will enable our advertisers to better target ads to specific types of visitors. 

ContentPop.com reserves the right to use and to disclose to third parties all of the information that ContentPop.com collects online about you and other visitors in any way and for any purpose, with one important exception. ContentPop.com will not use the information that it collects online from you while you are using the Service, nor will ContentPop.com authorize third parties to use such information, to mail or email promotional offers directly to you unless you have specifically informed ContentPop.com that you would like to receive promotional offers from ContentPop.com and/or from third parties. If you choose to receive these promotional offers, then your information may be used for direct mail or email marketing. 

Please also keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online – for example on message boards, through email or web logs, or in chat areas – that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides ContentPop.com. ContentPop.com cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third party use of such information. 

The ContentPop.com website includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third party products or services through the Service, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services. 

We also make some content, products and services available through our Service through cooperative relationships with third party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Service in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly; in which cases the privacy policy of the provider partner may apply to the provider partner’s use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly for more information. In addition, certain affiliated BLUE GUMBO divisions, such as other BLUE GUMBO websites, provide online services that are separate from our Service and may be subject to privacy policies that are different from ours. If you have any question about the privacy policy that applies to the online service you are using, you should click on the relevant link on the page of the service that you are using. 

Be aware that ContentPop.com may occasionally release information about visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Service agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our site, the public, or ContentPop.com. 

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that ContentPop.com, some or all of our assets, or our site is acquired by another company, information about our visitors may be among the transferred assets. 

## Children's Privacy Statement 

This children's privacy statement explains ContentPop.com’s practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding your rights under federal law with respect to such information. 

  * This Service is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service.
  * Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
  * We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Service.
  * Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we do NOT condition the participation in the Service’s online activities of a child under thirteen on providing personally identifiable information. 

## How To Make Changes to Your Information

Changes can be made at anytime by writing to us at the address listed below. 

## Questions Regarding Privacy

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of the ContentPop.com website, or your dealings with ContentPop.com, please contact us by writing to: 

Blue Gumbo  
523 East Beth Drive  
Phoenix, AZ 85042  |
